<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Lovesick</name>
    <directory>lovesick</directory>
    <id>2964089496</id>
    <description>Small mod (at the moment)
I aim at make something quite big with mods compatibility, add some lore and a way to make a character that evolves with your actions.
&quot;Open your heart or turn it into stone&quot;
And no more lore yet...

Including the first shielder of the game for the people that struggle with their skill issues.

The Faithfull

Starts with 1 red heart, one full bone heart and one soul heart.
Has the crow heart trinket gulped and the item Glaucoma.
This pocket item, the Locked Heart, will be explained with his main gimmick.

STRESS
Kinda stressfull tbh.

This character has a heartbeat that can't be muted (at the moment) that is linked with your stress.
The stress is in reality your heartbeat or BPM. It can raise up to 120 (240 with birthright).
On hit you lose 1/3 or 15 of stress, the mas amount between those two.
If it reaches 0, you are dead.

You gain stress when hitting enemies. The ammount is proportional to your dmg.
Your luck keep you stress at the middle, when not in combat.

Hitting enemies will deal bonus damage based on how stresses you are.
A flat dmg that goes from 0-2 times your dmg if near zero or 120 stress (with birthright goes from 0-4 at max stress)
A extra damage is dealt based on how many health has lost the enemy, up to a 0.05% at max stress.

The pocket active, Locked Heart, on use el spend one key and grant 15 shuel charges, that. will be spended blocking your own damage or co-op dmg, but also will block your extra g on high stress.
This active has synergies with all battery items.

The birthright doubles your max health, and adds a 30% of getting half red hearts killing.

Any  coder/spriter/help in general, msg me</description>
    <version>1.41</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
</metadata>
